<clxi>
<clxi>PROFILES
<clxi>
<clxi><char id="13">
<clxi><char id="14">
<clxi>Dark Knight Sparda
<clxi>
<clxi>
<clxi>
<clxi>
<clxi>
<clxi>Every once in a while you'll meet a lady<lf>so kind people call her a living saint.<lf>Well, I can safely say that in all my years<lf>on God's green earth, I ain't never met a<lf>girl that fit the bill like this here Kyrie.<lf><lf>These days you can find her looking after<lf>the little ones in an orphanage on Fortuna.<lf>After all the awful things that went down<lf>on that island, it's safe to say she's just<lf>about the only thing holding them poor<lf>folks together.<lf><lf>And don't get me started on how beautiful<lf>she is. She'd be beating the boys back with<lf>a stick if it wasn't for Nero.<lf><lf>Don't know what a sweet girl like that's<lf>doing with a punk like him, but hey...<lf>ain't none of my business. Different<lf>strokes, I reckon.
<clxi>Dante rescued this girl on one of his<lf>odd jobs. She had nowhere to go, so<lf>she started showing up at the original<lf>Devil May Cry. Heck, she'd even clean<lf>up since the man himself couldn't be<lf>bothered.<lf><lf>Eventually the little lady found her long-<lf>lost mama, and these days they live<lf>together under the same roof. Still, I hear<lf>she keeps showing up at Dante's to bug<lf>him from time to time.<lf><lf>Girl ain't afraid to tell Dante exactly what<lf>she thinks of his lazy ways, though from<lf>what Lady tells me, she's got a bright and<lf>bubbly way about her too.<lf><lf>Let's see what else we got here...<lf>Just turned 18, from the looks of it.<lf>Popular at school, popular with the<lf>fellas...dang, looks like she turns<lf>them all down though!<lf><lf>...None of this has anything to do with the<lf>task at hand, does it? Right, moving on...
<clxi>Wherever you go in the world, you can hear<lf>the legend of the Dark Knight Sparda:<lf>a demon swordsman who defeated the king<lf>of the underworld, sealing him away to<lf>protect his lady love. Shoot, good luck<lf>finding a kid who ain't heard the tale in<lf>this day and age.<lf><lf>Them Fortuna folks, though, they took it<lf>a step further...went and based a whole<lf>dang religion around the story! I mean, sure,<lf>there are records here and there substantiating<lf>the existence of Sparda, but only a handful<lf>of people know about 'em.<lf><lf>Mama told me stories of Sparda when I<lf>was a baby, but she thought it was just<lf>something you tell kids to get them to<lf>go to sleep. Daddy, though... Daddy was<lf>from Fortuna, so he believed in the whole<lf>shebang, though he never tried to make<lf>her drink the punch.<lf><lf>Maybe he figured she'd never believe him,<lf>or heck, maybe he was so head over heels<lf>he didn't give a flip what she believed.<lf>They ain't around anymore, so I can't<lf>exactly go and ask them. I can imagine<lf>what Mama'd say if I told her I partnered<lf>up with a bona fide descendant of Sparda.<lf>She'd have me strapped up in a straightjacket,<lf>for sure!<lf><lf>Sorry, Mama, but Sparda ain't just a<lf>fairy tale. Nero and Dante...them fellas<lf>are living proof.
